https://www.soundinsurance.com/privacy_policy

|
Home Of The Underdog!
Section title
Lorem ipsum (sample text) dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit. Sed luctus, viverra
Duis lorem lacus, porta quis, lobortis vitae, semper eu, massa.
Section title
Lorem ipsum (sample text) dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit. Sed luctus, viverra
Duis lorem lacus, porta quis, lobortis vitae, semper eu, massa.
Section title
Lorem ipsum (sample text) dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit. Sed luctus, viverra
Duis lorem lacus, porta quis, lobortis vitae, semper eu, massa.
Consumer Privacy Statement
Safeco appreciates the trust you place in us when you purchase insurance from one of our companies. We are committed to protecting your nonpublic personal information (“personal information”) and we value you as a customer.
To learn more about how Safeco collects and uses your personal information, please read the following notice.
Safeco’s sources of information about you
We collect personal information about you from different sources, including:
The information you provide on applications or other forms (such as your name, address and Social Security number);
Your transactions with us, our affiliates or others (such as your payment history and claims information);
The information we receive from a consumer reporting agency or insurance support organization (such as your credit history, driving record or claims history); and
Your independent insurance producer (such as updated information pertaining to your account).
Safeco’s use of your personal information
We only disclose personal information about our customers and former customers as permitted by law. Generally, this includes sharing it with third parties to administer your transactions with us, service your insurance policy or claim, detect and prevent fraud, or with your authorization. These third parties may include independent insurance producers authorized to sell Safeco insurance products, independent contractors (such as automobile repair facilities and property inspectors), independent claims representatives, insurance support organizations, other insurers, auditors, attorneys, courts and government agencies. We may also disclose your personal information to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. When we disclose your information to these individuals or organizations, we require them to use it only for the reasons we gave it to them.
We may also share information about our transactions (such as payment history and products purchased) and experiences with you (such as claims made) within our Safeco family of companies.
Safeco does not sell your personal information to others and we do not provide your information to third parties for their own marketing purposes.
Independent Safeco Insurance Agents
The independent insurance agents authorized to sell Safeco products are not Safeco employees and not subject to Safeco’s Privacy Policy. Because they have a unique business relationship with you, they may have additional personal information about you that Safeco does not have. They may use this information differently than Safeco. Contact your Safeco distributor to learn more about their privacy practices.
Information about Safeco’s web site
If you have internet access and want more information about our web site specific privacy and security practices, click on the Privacy Policy link on www.safeco.com.
Protecting your personal information from unauthorized access
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. Our employees are authorized to access customer information only for legitimate business purposes.
State Privacy Laws
This privacy statement may be supplemented by privacy laws in your state. We will protect your information in accordance with state law.
ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. SOUND INSURANCE AGENCY, COPYRIGHT © est. 1967-2019
FRIENDS OF THE UNDERDOG!
